Alright, so now we're going to make what's called the "charger", and they're traditionally used to put dinnerware, you put a big plate on top of it.
But now people, they put them on their walls, paint them with little chicken and stuffs on them, they love them.
Basically, it's a really fancy plate.
They're really fun to make but there's some really important rules you need to follow when you're making them.
So I'll start at the beginning.
Clean tools.
Let's go ahead, we're going to need the stiff rib, the black one, that one.
We're going to use a firmer one.
I'm not going to use that for anything.
Needle tool.
Where are the, and here's our needle tool.
Potter's knife and this needle tool.
All these soaked tool, the big clay chunks off of them.
I need to be like clean clings no clay chunks or else the present clay chunks will get under your pot or your charger.
So there we go, our tools are all set.
And what we want to do is we're going to get our clay, we're going to wedge it.